Quizizz Privacy Policy and Privacy Notice
=========================================

###### Updated and with Effective Date of Revisions

###### May 13, 2024

#### Contents

[Section 1. Protecting Students and their Personal Information](#section1)  
[Section 6. How Quizizz Collects Minimum Necessary Personal Information](#section6)  
[Section 14. Compliance With Laws. Policy Incorporates by Reference](#section14)  
[Section 15. Additional Policy Provisions for Specific Jurisdictions](#section15)  

[15.2. For Residents of the European Union (EU), United Kingdom (UK) and Switzerland](#section152)  

### Guiding Principles

##### Respecting your privacy is critically important to achieving our mission of motivating every student. These are our guiding privacy principles:

* We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
* We don’t keep your personal data, personal information or personally identifiable information (PII) (collectively referred to as “personal information”) longer than is necessary to provide our services to you.
* We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, provide our services, or protect our rights.
* We don’t rent, sell or exchange your personal information.
* We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what is (a) visible to the public, (b) seen by third-party search engines, browsers, platforms, websites, apps, or processors, (c) kept private, and (d) permanently deleted.

### General

This **Privacy Policy and Notice** (referred to herein as **Privacy Policy**) applies to users of the Quizizz platform and describes how Quizizz collects, uses, shares, stores, and protects your personally identifiable information and how you can access, update, delete, limit, and otherwise halt the use of this information.

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your personal information, including the option to use services without providing personal information. More details can be found in our [Quizizz Privacy Center.](https://quizizz.com/home/privacy-center?lng=en)  

Your use of the Quizizz services, website, and applications constitutes your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy and Notice, and your consent to Quizizz handling your personal data and information under these terms.

We strive to support as many people as possible, including those with disabilities. If a screen reader makes this policy more accessible to you, we recommend the following browser and screen reader combinations: Chrome and ChromeVox, Safari and VoiceOver (for Mac users), and Firefox and NVDA (for Windows users).

### Section 1. Protecting Students and their Personal Information

Quizizz believes the personally identifiable information of children and students deserves special protections and we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), the general consumer data privacy and student advertising limitation laws of US states and The General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). We also assist schools in meeting their obligations pursuant to the Family Educational Rights Privacy Act (“FERPA”).

Quizizz offers a limited feature set and website experience for young users of Quizizz. We do not require students to submit their name or contact information, nor do we require them to create accounts. When a student indicates that they are under the age when they can grant consent on their own, Quizizz does not collect personal information as defined under COPPA and may take additional steps to safeguard student privacy as required by law. Except as described in this privacy policy, Quizizz does not accumulate personal information about any child for distribution, sharing, or selling.

Here are some examples of safety and privacy measures on Quizizz:

* Students do not receive behaviorally targeted advertising.
* Students can join games without creating an account.
* The platform does not facilitate direct messaging between students.
* Quizzes are subject to proactive content filters and reactive reporting tools.

### Section 2. Parental Rights and Consents

**Quizizz empowers parents and legal guardians of children younger than the age of consent** (in the U.S., this means under 13) who have registered accounts with Quizizz, to exercise their legal rights pursuant to legislation such as COPPA. Parents/guardians can consent to collection and use by Quizizz of a child's personally identifiable information (PII) without consenting to the disclosure of information to third parties by Quizizz. Currently, the only personally identifiable information we collect from a child younger than the age of consent in any of the jurisdictions we operate in is their parent's or guardian’s email address. We may also collect a student’s first name, which alone is generally not PII but may be considered personal information in a generic sense.  

Parents/guardians may delete, modify, and review information their children shared with Quizizz by accessing their child's account. They may also create a parent account to manage their child’s access to Quizizz. Parents may also request that Quizizz delete that information and refuse to allow Quizizz to collect further information from their children by deleting their account at

[quizizz.com/settings](http://quizizz.com/settings) or otherwise contacting us at [privacy@quizizz.com.](mailto: privacy@quizizz.com) Quizizz may ask additional questions or take other steps to verify the identity of parents/guardians before responding to a request to review or delete their child's information, or a request to refuse further collection from children.

As necessary, Quizizz ensures that there is verifiable parental consent for children younger than the age of consent in any jurisdiction.

Quizizz offers consent options to parents so that users (or parents/ guardians) can consent to the collection and use of personal information necessary to provide the service without consenting to the use or disclosure of that information to third parties for other purposes (e.g., marketing).

Quizizz will never require a child to share more information than is reasonably necessary for using Quizizz. Quizizz uses, discloses and retains personal information only for the purpose of providing the classroom web app/software/service.

While Quizizz will assign persistent identifiers to all Quizizz users to recognize repeat visitors and improve their Quizizz experience, Quizizz does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children younger than the age of consent without a parent or guardian's consent. If we become aware, despite our intention not to gather this information, that we have collected personally identifiable information from a child younger than the age of consent without permission, then we will seek to obtain verifiable parental consent from the child’s parent or guardian to collect and use that data to provide the child with Quizizz services in the future; or, if consent is not provided, we will delete this information.

### Section 3. Information Quizizz Collects

#### 3.1. Sensitive Information

As described above, we limit data collection to what we need to provide the requested services. Quizizz does not knowingly collect data that is considered or defined as sensitive under any relevant country and state laws including COPPA, FERPA, CCPA, and other laws of the US, GDPR, and related laws in the EU, UK, Switzerland, and EEA, and similar laws in Canada, Australia, Brazil and other countries in which Quizizz provides its service, such as those related to race or ethnicity, health and biometric information, or political affiliation. In addition to these categories, we do not collect free or reduced lunch eligibility.

#### 3.2 Information You Provide to Quizizz

Accounts are not a prerequisite to using Quizizz, but are required to access some features and to save progress over time. If you create an account, Quizizz saves the account information you provide. This information may include: an email address, a parent or guardian email address, first name, last name, profile photo, or organization name.

Student profiles and activity within the Quizizz app and service are kept private and cannot be seen or collected by others unless their use of the app/service itself is collaborative and requires this type of sharing.

You may choose not to provide specific information or to delete or modify it at any time. These actions may prevent you from engaging with specific services or features that require this information. Additional information may be provided to Quizizz if you communicate with our support team, participate in user research, marketing campaigns or sweepstakes, or otherwise use the services.

If you engage in a financial transaction with Quizizz, we do not process or store this information beyond the transaction. Financial transactions are processed via a PCI-compliant payment provider and data is not stored by Quizizz.

As you use the service, you may also create academic content including quizzes and certain forms of responses. This information is not typically personally identifying, but it may be deleted at any time either by the relevant account holder or by reaching out to our team at [support@quizizz.com.](mailto: support@quizizz.com)

#### 3.3. Information Collected Automatically

We receive and store some types of information about how users visit our site and the devices they use automatically as you use the service. These may include device information such as device model, operating system, and device identifiers such as IDFA and UDID and network information.

Quizizz does not collect any personal information covertly, i.e., without the user’s knowledge, particularly audio/video information via the user’s own device.

Quizizz also collects log information as you use the service. These data may include information regarding how and when you use the service as well as your browser type, preferred language, time zone, referring site, log-in and log-out times, and internet protocol (IP) address.

We may use your IP address to generate a general approximation of your location to provide the service. Examples include providing the right version of Quizizz based on your state or country and helping teachers select their school when they sign up. Quizizz does not collect fine location data such as GPS or bluetooth beacons.

We use Google Analytics to help us understand how users engage with the service. Google Analytics uses cookies to compile reports that demonstrate how Quizizz is being used without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics at any time and continue to use Quizizz. To learn more about opting out, click [here.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

Aggregated demographic and activity data may be used for research purposes.

### Section 4. Information We Store; Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We conduct periodic reviews of accounts and may delete accounts that have been inactive for extended periods of time, normally not sooner than one year.

We may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

You may delete your account or update your information at any time by visiting [www.quizizz.com/settings.](https://quizizz.com/www.quizizz.com/settings)  

### Section 5. Information Shared with Third Parties

As described in this policy, Quizizz only shares your personal information when it is necessary to offer the service, comply with law, or with your permission.

#### 5.1. Third-Party Services that May Process Your Quizizz Personal Data

In order to provide and improve Quizizz, a limited number of third-party services require access to your personal information. For example, your account data are saved in a data center so that you can log in from any device. Third-party services are contractually prohibited from using your information except to provide the service. [A link to the table of the identity and type of our third party service providers,](https://support.quizizz.com/hc/en-us/articles/360037910691-Subprocessors-and-Service-Providers-Used-by-Quizizz)the purposes for which we use them and how they use and process personal data on our behalf can be found [here.](https://support.quizizz.com/hc/en-us/articles/360037910691-Subprocessors-and-Service-Providers-Used-by-Quizizz)

#### 5.2. Information from Other Third-Party Sources

Depending on how you use the service, we may also receive your personal information from another user, with a Quizizz educational account, under the Quizizz terms and conditions. For example, a teacher might input your email in order to share a quiz or parent report. If a teacher chooses to enter student information directly into Quizizz or requires students to sign up via the Google Classroom Integration, Classes on Quizizz, or a similar rostering functionality, teachers and schools are requested to get parental consent before using Quizizz with children who are under the age when they can grant consent on their own. A link to a usable template permission slip is available [here.](https://support.quizizz.com/hc/en-us/articles/23346678264857-Permission-Slip-Template-for-Teachers)

Content on Quizizz may contain links to other websites not affiliated with the service. While we review the privacy and security practices of third-party companies who assist us in providing you with our site and services, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites and users need to be aware of the data privacy practices of such sites should they choose to use these links.

#### 5.3. Third Party Cloud Provider: Amazon Web Services

Quizizz utilizes the services and infrastructure of outside parties to host its data. Quizizz holds those providers to a standard at least as protective of student data as the measures outlined in this policy. Our main cloud provider, Amazon Web Services (AWS), is the largest data hosting company and has leading practices in security standards and personnel in place to constantly monitor this area. A link to AWS’s Privacy Center can be found [here.](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy/)

#### 5.4. Google and Youtube API Services as Third-Party Provider

Google application programming interface (“API”) Services, including Google Sign-In, are part of an authentication and authorization framework that gives Quizizz, the ability to connect directly with Google users by requesting access to Google user data. The [Google APIs Terms of Service](https://developers.google.com/terms) govern the use of Google API Services when Quizizz requests access to Google user data.

Quizizz commits to adhere to the Google API Services User Data Policy, including its Limited Use requirements, for any data received from Google APIs. For more details, visit [Google APIs Terms of Service](https://developers.google.com/terms), [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy). Please check back from time to time as these policies are occasionally updated.  

Quizizz may collect information from partners and integrated technologies. For example, if you choose to use Google Login or join using the Google Classroom integration, we may receive information including your name and email address from Google. Quizizz does not have access to the passwords used to log into your Google accounts.

Quizizz also uses API Services of Google’s affiliated company, Youtube. Quizizz further commits to adhere to the[YouTube Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms) and to [YouTube’s Developer Policies.](https://developers.google.com/youtube/terms/developer-policies-guide)YouTube’s privacy practices govern the collection, use, and storage of user information by the YouTube API. By using Quizizz services, you acknowledge and agree to [YouTube’s Terms of Service.](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms)When an individual or user makes use of or accesses YouTube (whether through the YouTube API Services or otherwise), any use or access is governed by YouTube’s Terms of Service and Google Privacy Policy. Quizizz YouTube integrations use data and have access to information necessary for completing the project using YouTube. As the provider of YouTube API, Google’s privacy practices also govern the collection, use, and storage of user information by the YouTube API. By using Quizizz services, you further acknowledge and agree to the [Google Privacy Policy.](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

#### 5.5. Opt-Out Option

In order to use Quizizz services, you may opt out of any information transfer that is not strictly necessary to run the service, such as our data hosting cloud provider. However, all of our third-party providers adhere to strict data security standards. Generally, if any of our non-foundational suppliers are changed, you will not be notified. However, in the event of a change that has a material impact on how your data is shared, we will notify you by the same type of login notice detailed later in this policy, under the section on changes to the policy.

You have the right to delete, access, update, correct errors in, and export for transfer any of your personal information. Quizizz makes these data subject rights available to you regardless of which country or US state you reside in. Please see further detail below in section 11.2.

#### 5.6. Other Third-Party Details

Third-party services that transfer the personal information of EU residents are contractually bound to comply with GDPR. GDPR-specific information can be found in this Privacy Policy and Notice in Section 15 below.

Quizizz may need to disclose your information to a third party to comply with the law or a valid legal request. In such cases, we will let you know in advance, unless we are legally prohibited from doing so.

If Quizizz (or substantially all of its assets) are acquired by another company, personal information will be transferred to a new owner. In such a transfer, you will be notified and the new owner may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Quizizz may aggregate statistics about the behavior of visitors to our website and app to improve our services. For instance, Quizizz may monitor the most popular quizzes on the Quizizz site. Quizizz may display this information publicly or provide it to others.

### Section 6. How Quizizz Collects Minimum Necessary Personal Information

Quizizz collects only the personal information required to operate its classroom web apps, software and services. It does not access browser history, contact lists, search terms, preferences, device identification, location, etc. unless directly related to providing the service.

Quizizz does not condition a child's participation in a game, the offering of a prize, or ability to participate in any other activity on the child disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in such activity.

The information that Quizizz collects depends on the nature of the services you request. For example, fewer data are collected from a student joining a game without an account than from a teacher who creates an account in order to create quizzes and host games. Educators using Quizizz may create generic accounts or profiles for children using as little personal information as possible.

All interactions with the Quizizz website or app produce metadata that may identify you or could be identifiable information when paired with other information about you. In every case, Quizizz strives to collect only the minimum necessary information from you as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Quizizz or that is required by law. Visitors to the Quizizz website or app may always refuse to supply personally identifying information, however, doing so may prevent you from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Our classroom app and services allow adult educators and other users to make personal information, with created content by the user, available on-line. However, we do not permit personal information of children to be made available online.

### Section 7. How Quizizz Uses this Information

#### 7.1. We Limit All Disclosures

Quizizz uses the data we collect about you to operate, maintain, quality control, improve and develop and enhance the services we provide, secure information, develop new services, and protect our users and the company from security breaches or other unauthorized disclosures or uses.

Quizizz limits its disclosure of both information that could on its own or in combination with other information be used to identify you. We only disclose that information in order to (i) process it on Quizizz's behalf or to provide services available at Quizizz's website and mobile applications; and, (ii) agree not to disclose that information to others.

**Consent to Customer Reference.** Notwithstanding the above limits on disclosures, by using the Quizizz platform, services and/or educational or other products, you agree that, (a) if you are a paid account or business user, (b) a corporation or other business, school, school district or agency or other company, or (c ) an individual acting on behalf of one of the above entities, then (i) Quizizz may identify you as a customer and user of Quizizz services, and (ii) use your logo in sales presentations, marketing materials and press releases. Unless stated otherwise in a customer order, you agree to grant Quizizz a revocable limited license to use your organization’s name and logo solely to identify you as a customer of Quizizz, on Quizizz’s website, in marketing materials, presentations, or substantially similar formats. Quizizz will not identify any child or student as an individual user for any of these purposes.

#### 7.2. We Don’t Sell Student Information or Data

Quizizz does not rent, sell or exchange any data, including but not limited to, personally identifying information or potentially personally identifying information to any third party. Other than to Quizizz’s employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, Quizizz discloses potentially personally identifying information only when required to do so by law such as to comply with a court order, or when Quizizz believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property, or legal rights or safety of Quizizz, third parties or the public at large.

Quizizz does not benefit or profit from student personal information. Quizizz does not profile children for marketing purposes or in ways that lead to unfair, unethical or discriminatory treatment.

We do not monetize bid-stream data or audience data originating from child-directed or child-user content or traffic.

We do not repurpose student data or use it for research without express consent, and only if and unless authorized by statute or all data anonymized.

We securely destroy or make anonymous in a timely manner all personal information that is no longer required to provide the app/software/ service and they must explicitly identify retention timelines.

The information we collect helps us to provide the service, maintain a consistent experience, and improve it or develop new services. Examples of how this information is used include:

* Providing access to your account and saving progress over time.
* Personalizing your experience based on factors such as general location, preferred language and areas of study.
* Helping teachers identify and support individual students.
* Analyzing engagement with specific features over time.

We also use personal information to enforce our policies, comply with the law, and promote safety on the platform. These efforts protect the property, or legal rights or safety of Quizizz, third parties or the public at large. Examples of these efforts include:

* Preventing security breaches and fraud.
* Protecting users from inappropriate content.
* Verifying the identity of a user
* Complying with privacy legislation.

Quizizz may aggregate statistics about the behavior of visitors to our website and app to improve our services. For instance, Quizizz may monitor the most popular quizzes on the Quizizz site. Quizizz may display this information publicly or provide it to others.

#### 7.3. Communicating with You; Updates

If you are a registered Quizizz user, Quizizz may occasionally send you communications via email (if provided) or push notification (for mobile app users) to tell you about new features, get your feedback, and to keep you up to date with what's going on with Quizizz and our products. By registering to use our service you consent to the receipt of these communications, including text communications. You may choose to participate in sweepstakes and promotions which may have additional terms and conditions.

You may choose to stop receiving such communications by unsubscribing from emails and by disabling push notifications.

If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. We use de-identified queries and answers to build our knowledge base for users and to improve our products. We will not identify you in any posting or publication of your request. We will only engage in these activities where we have a legitimate interest, such as those stated above, and for de-identified data only, or with your consent.

### Section 8. Advertising and Marketing

Quizizz complies with all applicable laws and regulations regarding advertising, and specifically advertising on sites designed for and used by children. Quizizz does not allow or run personalized ads in its platform, make use of any third party trackers, or otherwise attempt to collect personal information from minors or on content sets as made for children.

Quizizz does not allow or display any third party advertising or marketing on its website or within our services.

Quizizz does not market third-party products or services to any of their users.

Quizizz may, from time to time, promote or publicize updates and extensions to the services it provides, and/or inform its users of new features or other information about the services. This is restricted only to Quizizz’s own services and not the services or products of any third party.

Quizizz does not permit any paid ads that incite children to purchase a product or service or urge parents or others to buy the item.

Quizizz does not permit any paid ads that incite parents or others to purchase a third-party product or service.

### Section 9. Changes to Privacy Policy and Notice

Quizizz reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy and Notice at any time, so please review it frequently. The most recent date of the policy, as set forth above, will show the date of the latest revisions.

We can also provide our most recent previous version of our Privacy Policy and Notice upon request by emailing privacy@quizizz.com.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy, so it is always in compliance with the current legal requirements and/or with industry groups standards or best practices, to more accurately reflect how data is processed through Quizizz specific systems, or to implement changes to services in the Privacy Policy, e.g., when introducing new services.

In this case, your future visits to our website will be subject to the updated Privacy Policy.

If we make a material change to our practices regarding your personally identifiable information, or publish an updated policy that has significant content changes, we will notify, by email before the change becomes effective.

Notice on our website means that after a material Privacy Policy and Notice update, you may not be able to access the Quizizz website or services without reviewing the updated information as it appears on your home screen upon login.

If you disagree with these changes, you may terminate and/or delete your account at any time and/or stop utilizing Quizizz or its services.

Your continued use of the Quizizz services, website and applications constitutes your acceptance of any changes to this Privacy Policy and Notice.

### Section 10. Openness and Transparency

Quizizz makes every effort to communicate privacy notices, terms of use, contracts etc., in clear, specific and unambiguous language that explains to users how their personal information is being used, processed, disclosed and retained by the provider and any third parties. In the event that any of our policies are unclear, please reach out to us to clarify and update.

### Section 11. Managing Your Personal Information and Data

#### 11.1. Data Subject Rights

You have the right to delete, access, update, correct errors in, and export for transfer any of your personal information. Quizizz makes these data subject rights available to you regardless of which country or US state you reside in.

#### 11.2. Managing Subsequent Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

As explained throughout this Privacy Policy, you have the ability to control the use of your personal information by Quizizz. If you wish to prevent Quizizz from using your information in any way whatsoever, you always retain your right to delete your account at any time. With the exceptions explained below for information you shared with other Quizizz users, this allows you to eliminate any subsequent use and disclosure of your personal information.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer want to use Quizizz, you may review, edit, or delete it by visiting Quizizz’ Settings page, found at [https://www.quizizz.com/settings.](https://www.quizizz.com/settings) Parents may remove, delete or update an account or any information concerning their child that is posted on Quizizz by visiting their child’s settings page, working with their child’s teacher, or by contacting us at [support@quizizz.com.](mailto: support@quizizz.com)

You have the right to erasure of your data, including metadata inferences, assessments and profiles (if not required for administrative purposes by the provider or the school board) and Quizizz does not charge a fee for this service.

Users are not required to surrender any copyrights to their own work if they post it to the Quizizz application or site. However, users grant a license for Quizizz to copy, use and distribute these works.

Users own their own personal information, data and created content. Users grant Quizizz a limited license to use the above for purposes set forth in this policy, including but not limited to, all uses related to providing the Quizizz product and services to students, educators and other users.

Certain activity on Quizizz may be displayed to other users, such as commentary on quiz content, blog posts, support articles, feedback forums or our blog, or the information on your Quizizz Profile and quizzes that you have made public. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. You may delete this information or change sharing settings directly. If you are unable to do this or need help, please contact our team at [support@quizizz.com.](mailto: support@quizizz.com)  

### Section 12. Data Security

#### 12.1. Standards

Quizizz follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.

Our security measures include the use of access-controlled data centers hosted in the United States, encryption of all data in transit, and the encryption of user password data both in transit and at rest. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, however, is 100% secure.

Quizizz reviews its Data Security regularly as part of its comprehensive security program in place that is reasonably designed to protect the security, privacy, confidentiality, and integrity of students’ and educators personal information against risks, (such as, unauthorized access or use, unintended or inappropriate disclosure) through administrative, technological, and/or physical safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information, as detailed within this policy.

Quizizz’s security program includes, but is not limited to, the following elements: enforcement of strong password protection, multifactor authentication, and full encryption of sensitive or confidential information.

Quizizz uses some outside parties to host its data and holds those providers to a standard at least as protective of student data as the measures outlined in this policy. Our main cloud provider, Amazon Web Services (AWS), is the largest data hosting company and has leading practices in security standards and personnel to constantly monitor this area.

* [A link to AWS Privacy Center can be found here](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy/).
* [A link to Quizizz’s Privacy Center can be found here](https://quizizz.com/home/privacy-center?lng=en).

#### 12.2. Breach Protocol

Quizizz has a detailed data breach protocol and checklist prepared in the event of beach. Our actions upon identifying a breach will include notifying you as soon as reasonably possible if the breach affects or may affect your data. In the event of a security breach, we will notify affected account holders within the amount of time required by law so that you can take steps to keep your data safe.

#### 12.3. Questions About Security Practices

If you have any questions about Quizizz security practices, you can contact us at privacy@quizizz.com. Quizizz reserves the right not to disclose our policies, procedures and the technologies and methods we employ to advance the security of your data to safeguard our practices.

### Section 13. Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to test new features and to help Quizizz identify and track visitors, their usage of the Quizizz website, and their website access preferences. Quizizz visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies, but some of the Quizizz website’s features may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

To learn more about “How Websites and Apps Collect and Use Your Information” including controlling cookies, please visit this [link.](https://consumer.ftc.gov/articles/how-websites-and-apps-collect-and-use-your-information#Controlling_Online_Tracking) You may also learn more about controlling flash cookies [here.](https://consumer.ftc.gov/articles/how-websites-and-apps-collect-and-use-your-information#Controlling_Online_Tracking)  

### Section 14. Compliance With Laws. Policy Incorporates by Reference

Quizizz complies with all applicable country, state and other applicable privacy laws in the places in which it provides its services. This includes but is not limited to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), state laws including but not limited to the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), which has been updated by the California Privacy Rights Act (CPRA), Virginia (VCDPA), Colorado (ColoPA) and other applicable federal and state laws in the United States; the European Union’s GDPR and related laws in non-European Union jurisdictions in which we do business (Switzerland and UK), Australia, Canada, Brazil and other applicable national laws and regulations.

Each of these sets of regulations and standards is hereby incorporated by reference with respect to any mandatory compliance elements. To see more on Quizizz compliance with specific state requirements, click [here.](https://support.quizizz.com/hc/en-us/articles/360051139551-State-and-District-Privacy-Agreements)

This Quizizz Privacy Notice and Policy is deemed and shall be read and construed to include all mandatory elements of these laws and regulations, and any conflict between this Notice and Policy and mandatory elements of any applicable regulations shall be read in favor of those laws and regulations.

### Section 15. Additional Policy Provisions for Specific Jurisdictions

The additional provisions in this section will generally apply as additional privacy protections for all users, even if not in the jurisdiction noted. However, in other jurisdictions these may be optional.

#### 15.1. Additional Information for California Residents

If you reside in California you are entitled to exercise certain rights outlined in the California Consumer Protection Act (CCPA).

You may delete your account or update your information at any time by visiting [www.quizizz.com/settings.](https://quizizz.com/www.quizizz.com/settings)

You may request access to the personal information we’ve collected by emailing our team at privacy@quizizz.com. Quizizz will not discriminate against you for exercising these rights.

#### 15.2. For Residents of the European Union (EU), United Kingdom (UK) and Switzerland

Quizizz Inc. is a U.S. company and the service is hosted in the United States. The information we collect is hosted on servers located in the United States. By using Quizizz, you consent to the transfer and processing of your personal information in the United States.

Quizizz shall ensure that the transfer is based on standard contractual clauses (“SCCs”) in the form currently approved by the European Commission.

Quizizz is committed to ongoing compliance with the “EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles” and the “Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Principles” (as applicable) regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from EU member countries, UK and Switzerland transferred to the United States pursuant to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (**EU-U.S. DPF**) and, as applicable the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF (**UK DPF**), and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (**Swiss-U.S. DPF**) .

Quizizz is committed to compliance with all applicable privacy laws and regulations of the EU, UK and Switzerland, primarily outlined in the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

GDPR is a regulation in EU law on data protection and privacy in the European Union (EU) and the European Economic Area (EEA); Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).

Quizizz is also cognizant of and committed to upholding the UK variations from or amendments to EU regulations on data privacy and security. The Data Protection Act 2018 (DPA 2018) is, in essence, the UK's implementation of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). All references herein to compliance with the EU GDPR principles and requirements shall apply equally with respect to Quizizz compliance with UK DPA 2018.

Quizizz is committed to the principles and rights for Data Subjects detailed in the GDPR with respect to Processing of Personal Data, including but not limited to:

* **Right of Access.** Right to obtain confirmation of which of your Personal Data is processed and information about it, for instance, which are the purposes of the Processing, what are the conservation periods, among others.
* **Right of Rectification.** Right to request modification of your Personal Data that is inaccurate or incomplete Personal Data, such as the address, VAT, email, telephone contacts, or others.
* **Right to Erasure or "Right to Be Forgotten”.** Right to erase your Personal Data, provided that there are no valid grounds for its retention, for example in cases where we have to keep the Personal Data to comply with legal obligation or because a court case is in progress.
* **Right to Data Portability.** Right to receive the Personal Data you have provided us in a digital format of current use and automatic reading or to request, if technically possible, the direct transmission of your Personal Data to another entity that becomes the new entity responsible for your Personal Data.
* **Right to Withdraw Consent or Right of Opposition.** Right to object or withdraw consent at any time to Processing, for example in the case of Processing for marketing purposes, provided that no legitimate interests exist prevailing over your interests, rights and freedoms, such as defending a right in a judicial process.
* **Right of Limitation or Right to Restriction of Processing.** Right to request the limitation of the Processing of your Personal Data, in the form of: (i) suspension of Processing or (ii) limitation of the scope of Processing to certain categories of Personal Data or purposes of Processing.
* **Right to Object and Automated Individual Decision-making -**When the Processing of Personal Data, including the Processing for the definition of profiles, is exclusively automatic (without human intervention) and may have effects in your legal sphere or significantly affect it, the User shall have the right not to remain subject to any decision based on such automatic Processing, except as otherwise provided by law.Further, the right to take appropriate measures to safeguard rights and freedoms and legitimate interests, including the right to have human intervention in decision making by us, the right to express a point of view or contest the decision taken on the basis of automated individual information processing.
* **Right to complain.** Right to complain to the supervisory authority, in addition to us. The exercise of rights is free of charge, except in the case of a manifestly unfounded or excessive request, in which case a reasonable fee may be charged regarding its costs. The information must be provided in writing but may be given orally if requested. In this case, we should verify your identity by means other than oral. The response to requests should be provided within a maximum of 30 days, unless it is a particularly complex request.

Definitions of some of the key terms specific to these areas and used in this Section are set forth below.

**“Consent of the Data Subject”** means any freely given, specific, informed and unambiguous indication of the Data Subject's wishes by which he or she, by a statement or by a clear affirmative action, signifies agreement to the Processing of Personal Data relating to him or her.

**“Controller”** means the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the Processing of Personal Data; where the purposes and means of such Processing are determined by Union or Member State law, the Controller or the specific criteria for its nomination may be provided for by Union or Member State law.

**“Data Subject”** refers to an identifiable natural person who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person. A Data Subject is any natural person whose Personal Data is being collected, held or processed. Examples of a Data Subject are an individual user, a customer, a prospect, an employee, a contact person, or other persons providing personal data.

**“Data Subject Request (DSR)”** means a formal request by a Data Subject to a Controller to take an action on his or her Personal Data.

**“Personal Data”** means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.

**“Processing”** means any operation or set of operations which is performed on Personal Data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.

**“Processor”** means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body who or which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller.

**“Recipient”** means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or another body, to which the Personal Data are disclosed, whether a third party or not. However, public authorities which may receive personal data in the framework of a particular inquiry in accordance with Union or Member State law shall not be regarded as Recipients. The Processing of those Personal Data by those public authorities shall be in compliance with the applicable data protection rules according to the purposes of the Processing.

Quizizz complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF (UK DPF), and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Quizizz has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and from the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. Quizizz has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF.

Quizizz has certified that it complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles, and, as applicable, the UK Extension and any UK specific modifications to the EU-U.S. DPF Principles as well as the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Principles, as applicable, with respect to such data.

If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and Data Subject rights under the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles, and, as applicable the UK Extension and any UK specific modifications to the EU-U.S. DPF Principles,or to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Principles, as applicable, then the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles, and, as applicable the UK DPF Extension and any UK specific modifications to the EU-U.S. DPF Principles as well as the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles, as applicable shall govern.

If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit Data privacy framework website.To learn more about the Data Privacy Frameworks, and to view our certification page, please visit [Data Privacy Framework website.](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/)

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF, Quizizz is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). We may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities.

Our accountability for personal data received in the United States under the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF and subsequently transferred to a third party is described in the Principles set forth above. Under the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF, Quizizz remains liable for the transfer of personal data to third parties acting as our agents unless we can prove we were not a party to the events giving rise to the damages. Details about how Quizizz shares information with third parties can be found in **Section 5** above. [A link to the table of the identity and type of our third party service providers,](https://support.quizizz.com/hc/en-us/articles/360037910691-Subprocessors-and-Service-Providers-Used-by-Quizizz) the purposes for which we use them and how they use and process personal data on our behalf can be found [here.](https://support.quizizz.com/hc/en-us/articles/360037910691)

In compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF, UK DPF, and Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, Quizizz commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information transferred to the United States pursuant to those principles. EU, UK and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints should first contact Quizizz by email at privacy@quizizz.com.

Quizizz has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-U.S. DPF, UK DPF, and Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism. If you have unresolved privacy or data use concerns that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider, free of charge, using the information provided at [https://www.jamsadr.com/dpf-dispute-resolution](https://www.jamsadr.com/dpf-dispute-resolution). This service is provided free of charge to you.

If your privacy concerns or complaints cannot be resolved through the above channels, under certain conditions, you may invoke binding arbitration for some residual claims not resolved by other redress mechanisms.

If you are located in the European Union, UK, Switzerland or the EEA, you have a right to lodge complaints about the data processing activities carried about by Quizizz. Our lead supervisory authority is the Austrian Data Protection Authority. You can find their contact details [here.](https://www.data-protection-authority.gv.at/)

We appointed GDPR-Rep.eu as representative according to Art 27.

GDPRhttps://prighter.com/verify/13361347 .

Our certificate of representation may be viewed at [https://prighter.com/q/13361347.](https://prighter.com/q/13361347)  
If you want to make use of your GDPR data privacy rights, please visit: [https://gdpr-rep.eu/q/13361347.](https://gdpr-rep.eu/q/13361347)

Contact information for our GDPR representative::

GDPR-Rep.eu at PrighterGDPR-Rep by  
Maetzler Rechtsanwalts GmbH & Co KG  
Attorneys at Law  
c/o Quizizz Inc.,  
Schellinggasse 3/10, 1010 Vienna, Austria.  
Please add the following subject to all correspondence:  
GDPR-REP ID: 13361347.  

Contact Information for UK Residents

Prighter Ltd (UK)  
Attorneys at Law  
c/o Quizizz Inc.,  
20 Mortlake Mortlake High Street  
London SW14 8JN  
UNITED KINGDOM  
Please add the following subject to all correspondence:  
GDPR-REP ID: 13361347.  

Quizizz has designated a GDPR Data Controller and GDPR Processor, as defined above, and uses industry standard compliance, directly and through its third party suppliers.

#### 15.3. For Residents of Australia

APEC Cross-Border Privacy Rules System and APEC Privacy Framework. Quizizz complies with the general principles and specific recommendations in the APEC Privacy Framework. Quizizz is committed to the main APEC privacy principles:

1. Accountability
2. Preventing Harm
3. Notice
4. Choice
5. Limitation on Collection
6. Limited Use of Personal Information
7. Integrity of Personal Information
8. Security Safeguards, and
9. Access and Correction

The Framework is intended to provide clear guidance and direction to businesses and government entities in APEC economies on common privacy issues and the impact of privacy issues upon the way legitimate business practice and government functions are to be conducted. It does so by highlighting the reasonable privacy expectations of the modern consumer. Businesses and member economies should respect individuals’ privacy interests in a way that is consistent with the Principles outlined in the Framework.

Quizizz is also cognizant of and committed to upholding Australian laws and regulations related to Data Privacy. The Privacy Act details specific rights, including, but not limited to, being told generally what kind of information we are collecting and how we collect it; why your personal information is being collected; that your personal information can only be collected for a lawful purpose, finding out what information we hold about you, the ability to have it corrected if it is incorrect, out of date or incomplete, and advising that your personal information must be stored securely and protected from interference or misuse. We make best effort to adhere to the 13 Privacy Principles contained within the Privacy Act:

1. Be Transparent
2. Allow Anonymity
3. Limit the Collection of Solicited Information
4. Handle Unsolicited Information With Care
5. Let Users Know How You are Collecting Their Data
6. Inform Users How You Use or Share Their Data
7. Limit the Use of Collected Information for Direct Marketing
8. Be Intentional When Sharing Information Across Borders
9. Follow Steps for Using Government Related Identifiers
10. Only Collect Valid Information
11. Keep Collected Data Safe
12. Give Users a Way to Access Their Information
13. Give Users a Way to Change Their Information

#### 15.4. For Residents of Canada

Quizizz Inc. is a U.S. company and the service is hosted in the United States. The information we collect is hosted on servers located in the United States. By using Quizizz, you consent to the collection, storage, transfer and processing of your personal information in the United States, as set forth in this Privacy Notice and Policy.

Quizizz is committed to ongoing compliance with all applicable Canadian federal and provincial privacy laws and regulations with respect to any data provided by its users in Canada.

Including but not limited to The Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA), as amended, and related provincial laws. British Columbia, Alberta and Quebec have enacted private sector privacy laws deemed “substantially similar” to PIPEDA, to which Quizizz adheres if applicable.

Quizizz acknowledges and agrees and adheres to the overarching guideline that any collection, use or disclosure of personal information must only be for purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate in the circumstances, as defined under PIPEDA.

Quizizz adheres to PIPEDA’s 10 fair information principles for the access to, collection, use and disclosure of personal information:

* **Principle 1 - Accountability.** An organization is responsible for personal information under its control. It must appoint someone to be accountable for its compliance with these fair information principles.
* **Principle 2 - Identifying Purposes.** The purposes for which the personal information is being collected must be identified by the organization before or at the time of collection.
* **Principle 3 - Consent.** The knowledge and consent of the individual are required for the collection, use, or disclosure of personal information, except where inappropriate.
* **Principle 4 - Limiting Collection.** The collection of personal information must be limited to that which is needed for the purposes identified by the organization. Information must be collected by fair and lawful means.
* **Principle 5 - Limiting Use,** Disclosure, and Retention. Unless the individual consents otherwise or it is required by law, personal information can only be used or disclosed for the purposes for which it was collected. Personal information must only be kept as long as required to serve those purposes.
* **Principle 6 - Accuracy.**Personal information must be as accurate, complete, and up-to-date as possible in order to properly satisfy the purposes for which it is to be used.
* **Principle 7 - Safeguards.** Personal information must be protected by appropriate security relative to the sensitivity of the information.
* **Principle 8 - Openness.** An organization must make detailed information about its policies and practices relating to the management of personal information publicly and readily available.
* **Principle 9 - Individual Access.** Upon request, an individual must be informed of the existence, use, and disclosure of their personal information and be given access to that information. An individual shall be able to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and have it amended as appropriate.
* **Principle 10 - Challenging Compliance.** An individual shall be able to challenge an organization’s compliance with the above principles. Their challenge should be addressed to the person accountable for the organization’s compliance with PIPEDA, usually their Chief Privacy Officer.

Canadian users with any privacy concerns or questions may contact Quizizz under the US contact information in Section 17 below.

#### 15.5. For Residents of Brazil

Quizizz Inc. is a U.S. company and the service is hosted in the United States. The information we collect is hosted on servers located in the United States. By using Quizizz, you consent to the collection, storage, transfer and processing in the United States, of your personal data (as defined under the laws of Brazil) and as set forth in this Privacy Notice and Policy.

Quizizz is committed to ongoing compliance with all applicable privacy laws and regulations of Brazil regarding data privacy, including but not limited to the Lei Geral de Proteção de Dados (LGPD), or General Law for the Protection of Privacy.

Quizizz recognizes the following aspects of LGDP regulations:

* Personal data encompasses “information regarding an identified or identifiable natural person.”
* Special restrictions for the processing of which is data that relates to racial or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, political opinion, affiliation to unions or political, philosophical or religious organizations, health information, sexual preference, or genetic and biometric data. Sensitive personal data may only be processed when the data subject specifically and distinctly consents to the specified purposes.
* Personal data may be processed without consent for certain specific and limited purposes.

Quizizz is committed to the fundamentals of personal data protection set forth in LGPD

1. \- respect for privacy;
2. \- informative self-determination;
3. \- freedom of expression, information, communication and opinion;
4. \- the inviolability of intimacy, honor and image;
5. \- economic and technological development and innovation;
6. \- free initiative, free competition and consumer protection; and
7. \- human rights, the free development of personality, dignity and the exercise of citizenship by natural persons.

Quizizz further adheres to the LGPD principles that govern data processing activities and set forth fundamental rights granted to all Brazilian data subjects. Under LGPD, processing of personal data activities shall observe good faith and the following principles:

1. **\- Purpose:** carrying out the processing for legitimate, specific, explicit and informed purposes to the data subject, without the possibility of further treatment incompatible with those purposes;
2. **\- Adequacy:** compatibility of the processing with the purposes informed to the data subject, according to the processing activity context;
3. **\- Need:** limitation of the processing activity to the minimum necessary for the accomplishment of its purposes;
4. **\- Free Access:** guarantee to data subjects free and easy consultation about the form and duration of the processing activity, and completeness of their personal data;
5. **\- Data Quality:** guarantee to data subjects accuracy, clarity, relevance and updating of the data, according to the need and for the fulfillment of the purpose of its processing;
6. **\- Transparency:** guarantee to data subjects clear, accurate and easily accessible information about the processing;
7. **\- Security:** technical and administrative measures capable of protecting personal data from unauthorized access and accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, communication or dissemination;
8. **\- Prevention:** measures to prevent the occurrence of damage due to the processing of personal data;
9. **\- Non-discrimination:** the impossibility of carrying out the processing activity for illicit or abusive discriminatory purposes;
10. **\- Responsibility and Accountability:** effective measures capable of proving observance and compliance with personal data protection rules, including the effectiveness of such measures.

Quizizz specifically highlights within LGPD, its acknowledgement and agreement with Article 14, Personal Data of Children and Adolescents, which requires the following:

The processing of personal data of children and adolescents shall be carried out in their best interest, in accordance with this article and the relevant legislation.

The following sections of Article14 have some references to other sections of LGPD and details omitted for use in this Privacy Notice and Policy:

1. The processing of personal data of children shall be carried out with the specific and prominent consent given by at least one parent or legal guardian.
2. In the processing of data … the controllers shall keep public the information on the types of data collected, the form of their use and the procedures for the exercise of the rights referred to in art. 18 of this Law.
3. Personal data of children may be collected without the consent referred to in § 1 of this article when collection is necessary to contact the parent or legal guardian, used only once and without storage, or for their protection, and in no case may be passed on to a third party without the consent referred to in § 1 of this article.
4. The controllers shall not condition the participation of the data subject referred to in § 1 of this article in games, internet applications or other activities to the provision of personal information beyond what is strictly necessary for the activity.
5. The controller shall make all reasonable efforts to verify that the consent referred to in § 1 of this article has been given by the parent responsible, considering the available technologies.
6. The data processing information referred to in this article shall be provided in a simple, clear and accessible manner, considering the user's physical-motor, perceptive, sensory, intellectual and mental characteristics, using audiovisual resources when appropriate, provide the necessary information to the parent or legal guardian that is appropriate to the child's understanding.

Brazilian users with any privacy concerns or questions may contact Quizizz under the US contact information in Section 17 below.

### Section 16. How to Contact Us.

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please send an email to [privacy@quizizz.com](mailto:privacy@quizizz.com), or write us at:  
  
Quizizz Inc.  
3110 Main St. Building C,  
Santa Monica, CA 90405  

Attention: Data Privacy

Any additional questions, comments or complaints may be addressed to our Data Protection Officer, Connor Pierson, who may be reached by either of these methods of contact.

© 2024 [Quizizz Inc.](https://quizizz.com/) | [Terms of Service](https://quizizz.com/tos) | [Privacy Policy](https://quizizz.com/privacy)
